SIDNEY HOWES

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



07735622158



✓ sidhowes@mail.com



35 Chestnut Avenue, Ewell, Epsom, Surrey, KT19 OSY

PROFILE

An ambitious, disciplined and hardworking individual keen to progress within the tech industry. Extensive experience working for a global company, with the ability to react well under pressure in a fast-paced environment - offering creative ideas.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Oualified Full-Stack Web Developer with code institute
- Diploma in Software Development
- Ex swimmer competed at national level
 - County Champion
 - London Champion
 - National Finalist
- Level 1 in sporting excellence within the swimming industry
- Level 3 NVQ in aerospace and aeronautical engineering
- Completed B1 modules in aircraft maintenance

SKILLS

HTML/HTML5

CSS/CSS3

JavascriptJquery

Django/Python

SQL/NoSQL Wordpress

EXPERIENCE

Code Institute

WEB DEVELOPER | DEC 2019 - DEC 2020

British Airways

AIRCRAFT ENGINEER | OCT 2018 - OCT 2020

British Airways

AIRCRAFT MECHANIC | SEP 2015 - OCT 2018

British Airways

AIRCAFT APPRENTICE | SEP 2012 - SEP 2015

Abercrombie & Fitch

SALES ASSISTANT | SEP 2010 - SEP 2013

EDUCATION

Code Institue

DEC 2019 - DEC 2020 Diploma in Software Development

Kingston College

JUN 2012 - JAN 2015

Level 3 NVQ Aeronautical and Aerospace Engineering

Glyn Technology School

SEP 2006 - JUL 2012

10 GCSE's ranging between A* - C

OTHER EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

- Buro Happold Civil Engineering
- Millwall football club involved with the development of the academy players
- Physical Education teacher/assistant Hinchley **Wood Primary School**